The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world
and to become the next Wizard King.
The Clover Kingdom.
Dad Rick Re sees another some song about Aaron Smith.
I'll see you next time.
But he controls Salamander now, too.
And there's Lord Nozel.
His bangs are dreamy.
I heard that he was on the front lines during that last battle.
Lady Charlotte!
I don't see Yami or the green praying mantis, Captain.
How dare they be late on an important occasion such as this?
There's Rell!
Uh, is he okay?
Looks like he's spacing out there.
Oh, yeah.
I know that face.
He's definitely in love.
That wonderful girl.
I wonder where she is now.
Mr. Rill's first love.
Great news, madam.
Your precious little boy is starting to become a man.
I'd say it's only a matter of time before you'll be a grandmother.
Wow, look.
It's Lady Dorothy.
He's awake.
Who knew she had such pretty eyes?
Hey there.
How is everybody?
Lord Kaiser looks awfully dapper today.
Yeah, but he seems a little down.
Huh.
Check it out.
The man of the hour!
Wizard King!
Oh no, is he injured?
I guess so.
I heard he was the one who stopped the eye of the midnight sun back when they attacked the
royal capital.
Goodness, he must have been through such a terrible ordeal to protect all of us.
I hope he isn't in too much pain.
We'll never forget what he did.
Go Wizard King!
What?
You want me to pose as you?
That's ridiculous!
Perhaps, but I can't exactly go marching into the capital looking like a child.
There'd be trouble if the king saw me this way.
And of course, not appearing at all would be suspicious.
True, but don't you think they'll know the difference?
I've already thought through the whole thing.
All you have to do is stand up there and wave.
Here, cover your face with these.
What?
Your appearance is different now, but inside you're the same as you ever were.
Just smile and wave and pray they don't notice.
We're sorry.
The Wizard King has a sore throat today, so sadly he won't be able to speak to you all.
Please excuse him.
Oh, I was looking forward to hearing from him.
Well, these things happen.
Yeah.
Now, I'd like everyone to give a round of applause to the valiant hero who stood up to our enemies
and protected our beloved kingdom, our illustrious ruler, Augustus Kiriclover XIII.
Oh, hey, he's here, too.
He's okay, I guess.
Thanks for your help.
Why are you dawdling back there?
Pick up the pace, knave!
This is my one moment of glory, you know!
Sahari!
Oh, how the heck did I end up being errand boy to this king?
It turns out going with the flow is for chunks.
How dare you stand in my royal bubble!
Same goes for you!
Curse you, Julius.
Now I'm responsible for addressing the people, all because you have a little tickle in your pathetic throat!
Then again, this might be the perfect opportunity to demonstrate my superior dignity and benevolence!
You poor fool!
I hope you enjoyed the attention while it lasted!
Ahem!
Greetings and salutations to all my loyal subjects!
Your king, Augustus Kiriclover XIII, is gracing you with his presence!
What's this?
They're at a loss for words!
They must be stunned by my immaculate visage!
Is he almost done, or...?
Shhh...
Yes.
As you can see, the public awaits your kingly wisdom with bated breath, Majesty.
But please make it as brief as possible, lest the suspense kill them.
Uh, of course!
I beg your pardon!
The king takes orders from no one!
Ahem!
Thanks to my brave deeds with minimal assistance from the magic knights,
the Eye of the Midnight Sun has fled,
and peace has finally been restored to the Clover Kingdom!
You're so welcome!
None of this would have been possible without the impressive things I do on a daily basis!
However, I imagine some of you are still concerned.
How will your lives change?
What if another enemy tries to attack us?
But I promise there's no need for that!
Hawk!
Witness my splendid light magic!
How majestic!
How striking!
Light magic!
Absolute monarch of divine brilliance!
Perfection!
And so, my adoring public!
As long as the Clover Kingdom remains in my capable hands,
it shall always be safe!
Lay all your cares and doubts upon my shoulders!
Damn it!
That's enough, Beanpole!
Let's settle this feud once and for all!
Care, care!
You don't have to ask me twice!
Time to put your money where your mouth is, foreigner!
Hey, wait!
What's going on?
What is this, a party?
Yami, Jack...
I know, I told you to.
We had an important event planned today.
We were supposed to gather in the square and tell everyone that the enemy's been defeated.
Oh, was that today?
Care, care!
Must have slipped my mind.
Picking unnecessary fights is not an acceptable reason to show up late!
Trust me, he's the one who started it.
That's a lie!
We were both there, you know damn well what happened.
I think we've heard enough from the two of you.
This is hardly the time or place.
Tch!
Goodness, both of those squads are so violent!
You saw the paper, right?
They say one of the black bulls is possessed by a devil.
That makes sense.
When they placed second at the Star Festival, I knew they must have had outside help.
Exactly.
Everyone knows they're the worst squad.
Why, you irreverent ingrates!
How dare you intrude upon my invincible light magic spell!
Huh?
Your what?
Don't test me!
You brute stepped right into my spotlight!
Your highness, perhaps this is a chance to show the people your leniency.
If they see how merciful you are, they'll like you more.
Oh, is that so?
Who wants your opinion?
Just because you've been hailed as a hero, give me a break!
I mean, I must applaud your fervor.
By all means, gentlemen, keep being your raucous selves.
It's a symbol of your passion for our great land.
Sure.
And now his majesty will take his leave.
Let's give him one more round of applause.
Um, excuse me, Captain Jack.
Look, anytime you want me to come back to the praying mantises, just give me a holler.
Come back?
Who the hell are you?
Attention to me, servant boy!
Uh, be right there.
Is he one of your guys?
You really think I let a wuss like that on my squad?
I suppose it's about time for us to head out as well.
Yeah, I guess.
Okay, later!
Lord Vondance!
Thank goodness it's over.
You gonna explain your outfit, Doc?
Or do we have to guess?
What?
Yikes!
All of the Magic Knight captains in the same room!
Kind of hard not to feel like we're under a lot of pressure.
Yeah, if this is supposed to be a meeting for captains,
then I wonder why they wanted all of us to be a part of it.
I should apologize, Yami.
You and the Black Bulls are the ones who deserve that praise.
And yet the audience mostly cheered for me.
We're kind of used to getting booed, actually.
Right, I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Just forget about it.
Calm down.
Don't let your heart go aflutter.
Just relax and breathe.
What's wrong, prickly princess?
Your face is all red.
Feeling okay?
I'm perfectly all right!
Listen...
If you need to take a dump, it's not healthy to hold it in.
Just go.
That's not the issue at all!
How can a person be so utterly devoid of tact?
So I was wrong?
Dead wrong!
You really don't get it, do you, Yami?
No wonder everyone's calling you a clueless idiot.
He needs to piss!
No!
And they're in charge.
Are they like that all the time?
I wish this was shocking to me.
Forcing us to come to a meeting and then being the last person to show up, if that's not typical Julius, I don't know what is.
I bet you anything he forgot about all this.
He's probably off goofing around somewhere like a little idiot.
Crazy old man.
A crazy old kid, I guess.
I hate to say it, but you're right.
Shameful.
Yeah, that's true.
He's so silly.
Agreed.
Any idea what his problem is?
Nope.
He's been stuck like that since the curse broke, apparently.
I'm sorry for the wait, everyone.
Excellent.
I see you all made it.
Him again?
The Matio.
They asked him to come too?
Pardon the delay.
Careful.
If you try to condemn one of my squad members again, I swear I will...
Yami, I'm the one who summoned him here, so there's no need to fight.
Wait, you were invited?
So it would seem.
Apparently, the topic in question involves me.
I was informed that my presence was required.
Our meeting today is about the devil residing in the Spade Kingdom.
Recently, some of our magic knights paid a visit to the Heart Kingdom,
hoping to gather information about the devils.
I trust everyone's seen the reports by now.
However, since you all were there, we would like to hear it from you.
Please proceed.
Okay.
We'll do our best, sir.
In the Heart Kingdom, the strength of a mage is normally determined by a system called magic stages.
The ranking starts at nine, then eight, seven, and so on.
And the smaller the number, the stronger the mage.
According to Queen Laura Pechka, it's extremely rare and favorable to have mages at stage zero.
So whenever there's a battle, the side with the most warriors at that level is considered the superior one.
And this is the most important part of what we've learned.
If we go up against the devil, we won't stand a chance unless everyone is at least stage one.
A stage one, eh?
Right.
To see her one
So to sum everything up, I've called this meeting so we can decide the best way to provide aid to the Heart Kingdom.
Queen Laura Petchka plans to invade the Spade Kingdom in six months' time, before she becomes too weak.
We're considering deploying our own forces to fight alongside them.
I'm asking each one of you to make sure your squads are as strong as you can.
We only have six months, but please do everything possible to raise their stages to one.
We must defeat Spade to protect the residents of Heart, as well as our own land.
I've been informed by Queen Laura Petchka that the Spirit Guardians are also going to contribute.
Can I count on you?
Yes, Wizard King.
Of course.
As if you needed to ask me, my team has already started.
I told the Black Bulls they could do things however they see fit over the next half a year.
Yes, William?
I'll participate in the battle. However, as you all know, the things I did in the past were unforgivable,
and I believe I am no longer worthy of facing my squad as captain.
And so, with a heavy heart, I request that you relieve me of my position.
Huh?
Wait!
If you would, sir, I'd like you to assign me a new mission.
It would be an honor to put my life on the line to help overthrow this devil.
Captain Fongens...
If he's to blame in this, then so am I.
Although my body was possessed by an elf at the time, I have committed unspeakable crimes.
I should be put to death.
I failed as well. It isn't right to call myself a captain.
Eh, I don't feel all that bad about it, actually.
Oh, really? Cause you should.
Alright, I've heard enough.
I understand why some of you may be feeling ashamed of what happened.
That being said, I cannot and will not take away your responsibilities as captains.
If I did, I'd have to extend the same treatment to the other magic knights who fell under control of the elves,
and that's a lot of people to punish.
Without them, we'd hardly have anyone left to guard our land.
If you truly want to atone for your actions,
your only option is to forget your titles and work together to protect the Clover Kingdom.
I'm putting my complete trust in you all.
Sir!
As your command.
Roger that!
For you, Wizard King.
So, Damnatio, does this arrangement work for you?
How do you mean, sir?
As we established, the magic knights need to train for the next six months
in order to be successful in their battle against the Devil.
Asta's still waiting to receive a sentence.
But surely you can table that decision until after this is dealt with, yes?
I suppose I don't object.
But let me be quite clear.
I've chosen to cooperate only because I believe this is the most beneficial strategy
for the Clover Kingdom at large.
Now, please excuse me.
I know where he can shove those damn scales.
Wow, you really got me off the hook, Wizard King. Thank you so much.
There's no need to thank me.
Okay, but I'm super grateful.
Anyway, I'm expecting great things from you.
Keke!
You can depend on me!
I can't wait to slice up my subordinates!
That's one way to trim the fat!
Not the point.
This'll be fun!
I'll start creating our training regimen immediately.
Actually, it might be best if all the squads do this together.
That's a good idea. We could hold mock battles.
Keke! I'm not holding back!
That's my line, freak!
Perhaps we should go ahead and enlist a few healing mages.
I'm sure we're going to need them.
Don't get too carried away.
This is as good a time as any.
Marx, why don't you bring him in now?
Yes, sir.
Hey, it's the Hamhawk again.
Obviously all of you are familiar with Gelder Poizat,
the former captain of the Purple Orcas.
He was recently caught in a crime, robbing the Shadow Palace.
He and Revchi, the disgraced former magic knight who was once his superior,
managed to get away with an enormous haul of precious gems and ancient magic items.
Scum.
Honestly, when will you ever learn?
I can't wait any longer!
I'm going to slice this ham into little bite-sized pieces!
I'd be doing the kingdom of service, right?
That's not necessary.
Because I've been thinking I might like to pardon Gildare instead.
Pardon him?
What?
This man happens to have a great talent for business.
I believe he's capable of turning an impressive profit
by selling the very treasures that he attempted to purloin.
I'd like him to use that extra money for the benefit of the Clover Kingdom.
The repairs we've been doing are far from cheap after all,
and we don't exactly have access to infinite financial resources.
You'll lend us your services, won't you?
Well, I don't know.
Suddenly my life depends on whether or not I can make a business deal!
Please?
Yes, your highness. I swear, I'll do everything I can!
Thank you. This is a big help.
Uh, of course.
He made him an offer he couldn't refuse!
He's pushy like Yami, but way sneakier!
You better make sure you fetch us a good price at the market, little piggy.
That's right! Because if you screw this up, you're going straight to the chopping block!
There's just one more thing.
As I explained to you all a few moments ago,
we do have certain limitations when it comes to our finances.
Therefore, in order to alleviate the financial burden caused by our situation,
I'll need to reduce your pay by 50%.
A logical solution, indeed.
I can accept that.
It's fine with me.
Yeah, it's okay.
No sweat!
It's no problem at all.
That's the least that I could do.
Well, that settles it, then.
Uh, I don't think so!
Not happening!
Is something wrong?
Come on, man! I'm in debt! You can't just cut my pay!
Do you want us to go broke?
Remember, your subordinates are present.
Be an example.
This is my example!
Well, we decide these things based on majority, so...
Reduced pay it is!
With that, we now conclude the Magic Knight Squad Captain's meeting.
What a load of crap!
How long do you plan to act like drunken fools?
I can't endure this.
Fine! Go home then, nerd!
We can't expect you to care!
Yeah, you nobles are rich anyway!
You probably won't even notice the difference when you lose half your pay!
This is nonsense.
I'd wish you'd learn to drink in moderation.
Bye! Don't throw up!
I'll throw up!
I bet your old golden guts can stick around!
Yeah, you got time!
Come on, heroes! Save the kingdom!
Do us a favor and join us for a quick game!
Game?
We'll get our salary back by making you gamblers away!
Fine, I'll play.
We're about to clean you out!
Typical.
I won again.
I got three times my page.
I'm truly grateful to both of you.
Despite what happened, you haven't treated me the least bit differently.
You have my word. I'm going to do everything in my power to defeat that devil.
Good night then.
Here you are, sir. I'm sorry my friends made such a racket.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.